Cantonese Subtitles www.cantocaptions.com
Mom
Dad
Bingo
Bluey
- Mom
- I'm not your mom
I mean Dad
Yes
Can we play hide-and-seek now?
Wait a moment
Why is that stone dog statue just sitting there?
He's practicing not getting distracted.
What? You don't need to practice something like that.
Are you really sure?
Yes.
It's easy not to get distracted, watch.
Oh, it's a dragonfly!
Carrot sticks.
Hey, Bingo, let's play hide-and-seek.
Okay, let's play hide-and-seek!
This Bluey story is about
[Hide-and-Seek]
Okay, you guys hide.
I'm going to catch you, start!
One, two...
Wait a moment.
-Yeah, wait a moment.
-Wait a moment.
If you want us to hide,
Then you have to promise to not just play a little
and then go play with rocks.
I've never done that!
- Yes, you have!
Okay... I promise.
- Good.
Start now!
- One, two, three...
- Yay!
Oh no, Bingo, she's counting!
Hurry up, we need to hide!
Six, seven, eight...
Don't get distracted!
Ten, eleven, twelve...
Thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
Sixteen, seventeen...
Eighteen, nineteen, twenty!
Are you ready yet? I'm coming to get you!
Okay, let's think about where they might be hiding first.
Oh, it's a tennis ball.
Oh, can't get distracted, Bluey.
They're not here either.
They're really hiding well.
Is anyone here?
Ji-Ja-Jai!
I thought I had lost you.
Are you hungry, Ji-Ja-Jai?
Feed me!
I want to feed you, but...
I'm supposed to be playing hide-and-seek right now.
Okay, I'll quickly feed you a little something.
I don't understand why you went inside the sink cabinet.
Feed me!
Okay, where's the stuff you like to eat?
Ji-Ja-Jai, I know, I'm looking for it.
Found it!
Ji-Ja candy!
Here, for you.
Delicious...
Alright, I need to go back to catching them.
Bathroom...
Oh, Ji-Ja-Jai.
Poo-poo...
Okay, go on, do your business.
Alright, Ji-Ja-Jai.
I must excuse myself.
Okay, what was I doing just now?
Finished toilet…
Ji-Ja-Jai probably needs help washing his hands.
Why is it so dirty here?
Yes, very interesting.
Wash…
All done, Ji-Ja-Jai, no more germs.
Okay.
I have to go back to...
I forgot what I was supposed to do!
Oh, alright then.
I think I'll just play with you.
It feels so good to see you again, Polly.
You have to tell me everything.
Tell me about your trip to Egypt.
Okay, it was so much fun!
Do you need some milk in your tea?
Yes, please.
Yours, Polly.
Do you want any, Shirley?
Ji-Ja-Jai!
This is a tea party, not a dance party!
Please don't be so loud!
I'm so sorry that my husband is being so rude.
Stop, don't!
He's always like this.
I'm sorry, Ji-Ja-Jai.
It's obvious we can't play together like this.
I'm just going to turn you off for a little bit.
Why don't you have a switch?
Mom, help me take out Ji-Ja-Jai's batteries!
Be quiet, Ji-Ja-Jai.
Mom!
Where are you?
Dad!
Bingo! Bingo!
Why isn't anyone answering me?
Ji-Ja-Jai, that's enough.
Where have they all gone?
Okay, I really need some peace and quiet to think this through.
One, two, three, four.
Oh, that's right, I remember now.
-Found you!
-Nice!
Found you!
For real...
The Christmas tree was poking my back the whole time!
Can you guys believe it?
I got distracted.
I actually forgot we were playing hide-and-seek.
- We believe it.
That's so typical of you.
Now you guys hide, I'm going to catch you!
- Okay!
One, two, three, four...
Hurry, hide quickly!
Bingo only knows how to count to 14.
Oh, a dragonfly!
- Hurry up and walk! - Ten, eleven, twelve…
Thirteen, fourteen…
Ready yet? I'm coming to catch you!
Where could they have gone?
They might be hiding in…
The trash can!
They're not here.
That's right, Bluey.
What did you do with the Ji-Ja-Jai?
Oh, don't worry.
I put him in a very peaceful place.
They might be hiding in...
Here, found them!
Cantonese Subtitles www.cantocaptions.com