Cantonese Subtitles
www.cantocaptions.com
Mom
Dad
Bingo
Bluey
-We're back!
I'm so tired today
Come chop some wood, kids
-Yeah!
-Chop...
Wooden
It's time for bed in five minutes, kid.
Let's wait another five years before going to this crazy world again.
Let's play a game instead.
You can play a game, but there are conditions.
The game must be one where I don't have to move or speak.
Okay.
Bingo!
Let's pretend Mom and Dad are mountains.
Yay! Mom and Dad mountain!
This time, Bluey's story is about
"Mount Mumandad"
Let's race to the mountaintop
The first one to plant a flag on the summit wins
Get ready
Go!
Wait, I need climbing gear
It's tall, but we only have five minutes
Don't start without me
Got everything
Get ready to start
Wait, I forgot to bring the music box
That's enough, Bingo
I'm not waiting anymore, I'm starting
I'm ready
Hey, if you don't wait for me, I'll start
How long do you expect me to wait for you?
Then I have to go back and get some very important mountaineering equipment
It's so hard to climb!
Because your backpack has too many things
It's heavy, so it's hard to walk.
It's all mountaineering gear.
And Mom and Dad's hiking map.
That's right, it means I'm not going the wrong way.
Oh, it's Bingo.
The scenery on the mountain is beautiful.
This mountain really stinks.
I'm about to beat you, Bingo.
Let's take a picture...
Bingo, what are you doing here?
We are racing
Taking photos… oh, that’s right
It must be very difficult to get over there
Help, I’m sliding down
Help me, Bingo
I’m coming
Don’t worry, Bluey
There’s a rope in my backpack
Here, grab on
Got you, Bluey
Hold on!
That was just luck
Thank you, Bingo
You're welcome
But I'm still going to beat you
Bluey
Oh no, this slope is too steep
And it's slippery too
Bingo
Can I use your head to get some leverage?
Hey!
Sorry!
Bluey
I'm about to beat you, Bingo
How could you do that?
That's cheating!
I'm not cheating!
Yes, you are cheating!
No, I'm not cheating!
No, I didn't cheat!
It's ruined!
Dad, stop!
This time it's ruined, it's an avalanche!
Bluey, are you okay?
I'm fine
It's just a small avalanche
It won't stop me from getting to the summit
Bluey, a storm is coming!
Dad
Stop it quickly!
Bluey, hurry up and come down
It's very dangerous up here!
I can't, I'm almost at the summit
Bluey, come into the tent
I can't, I must reach the summit
You can't handle the storm
Dad
This ancient mountain is really terrible
I quite like your tent
Thank you
It's for you
That's great
Thank you, Bingo
We can play London Slapjack and wait for the storm to pass
Good idea
Black taxi
Trafalgar
Man in a furry hat
Buckingham Palace
-Slap!
After that
The rabbit ran very fast...
So he left behind a very slow turtle
Run faster, turtle
Yeah, run faster
Must beat that mean rabbit
It seems the storm hasn't stopped yet
So what should we do?
Then let's stay in the tent
We can watch the ballerinas spin.
Bingo, I'm sorry for cheating.
It's okay.
Sometimes I'm the bad rabbit.
Then I'm the slow turtle.
Bingo, that big storm has stopped.
The morning mountain is quiet now.
Here we go, let's walk.
No problem.
Don't wake this ancient mountain.
If you want to successfully climb Mount Mumandad,
You cannot merely rush forward on your own
Or leave your opponents behind to succeed
But rather, you must slowly, carefully
Rely on teamwork in order to succeed
This is the way of mountain climbing
Cantonese Subtitles
www.cantocaptions.com