As if in a dreamland
Magical powers given to me
The bag's treasures
Traveling together in the universe
Capturing above the galaxy
The beauty of time
If problems are encountered
Transforming anytime and anywhere, seemingly full of inspiration
Quickly fly to a delightful and carefree paradise
Holding hands with the starlight
Dancing and shimmering
Casually step through this door
Achieve ideals, dreams come true
Across railways and the countryside
In an instant, the Dream Express reappears
sha la la la la
Accompany me to sing together
Singing Encore loudly
Let's go have fun marching
Doraemon
Let this moment not grow old
Dreams can finally be achieved
sha la la la la
Accompany me to sing together
Singing aloud
Let's go for a stroll together
Doraemon
Let this moment not grow old
Beautiful scenery will be seen
[Moving House with a Relocation Map]
Nobita, you're late again!
That's right...
Nobita, you're outrageous!
You're always late!
Why are you so slow at everything you do?
You just need to leave a little earlier!
I know, but...
I, for one, have never been late!
Because my house is right next to the school
You're so lucky
Mom, I have something to ask you
Something to ask me, what is it?
Can we move next to school?
Living closer to school means I won't be late anymore
Don't say such impossible things!
You just need to wake up earlier!
There are still other ways...
We could just move the school next to our house
Move the school?
Just use this!
"Relocation Map"
First, call out the place you want to move the building to
Our district!
That's the school
This is this house
First, peel off the school sticker
Then peel off the stickers of the houses in front of our house
Swap them and stick them all back down, done!
What happens after that?
Look out the window and see
Like this?
The school is right in front of the house!
It will become the same as the map
Amazing!
This way you won't have to worry about being late anymore
Thank you, Doraemon
So Nobita's house is this close?
Oh, right
I should pay Nobita's house a visit
Well, I just needed to make a surprise visit
to talk about Nobita's score disparity
Please be stricter
Urge Nobita to study harder
Yes
Next time
If you don't get a better score, I won't let you go!
Outrageous
First of all
Go to the bank, then go to the supermarket
What should we have for dinner?
Thinking about it, school so close to home isn't that great
As long as you are willing to study a bit more seriously
then there won't be any problems
Don't say such discouraging things
Nobita
Sorry, this is an urgent letter
Go to the post office and mail it for me right away
By the way, buy me some stamps
To the post office? It's a long way to walk
Okay, we'll move the post office
next to our house!
Okay, swap this one and this one
Here, Dad
So fast?
So clever!
Move some more over here, we can make it even more convenient!
Okay!
Let's turn the back of the house into a park
Let's put Shizuka's house next to ours
Now I can see Shizuka every day with ease!
Becoming neighbors, there will still be such things
In order to be able to play conveniently
Put the vacant lot next to us
Full attack, Gian!
- So sorry!
Huh? This isn't Mr. Shigemi's house?
It's Nobita's house
Gian, Suneo
Nobita
What are you doing?
You can change this area however you want with this?
It sounds interesting
Let us try it too
Okay!
First…
Move the toy store next to my house
Move the bookstore that sells a lot of comics over here
Move the shop that sells red bean paste buns here
That's right
My home should also move near the open lot
You mean near my home?
If you want to move
How about moving to a more open place
Oh, that's good
No…
Isn't near the school better?
Convenient, right?
Oh, yeah, that sounds good
But there are so many mansions here
Right
Why don’t you move to a place with a better view?
That's good too
Here is good
Are you guys
Really unwilling to be near me?
No, how could that be?
No, no
Alright, we need to hurry back
Huh? It seems to have changed since just now
There's a house like this here?
Which direction is it?
Uh... let me think...
I remember now, it's that intersection
Change it a bit more!
- Yes!
- Hey, Nobita!
Doraemon!
- Yes!
- How about this one?
- Okay
Mom went out to buy something, but she's taking a long time to come back
Did he say anything?
Could it be...
Mom got lost and can't find her way home?
Quick, we have to go pick up Mom!
Mom!
Where on earth did Nobita go?
Suneo, how about we think of something...
You ought to move something more interesting here.
Oh, is that so...
There's also a piece of paper stuck to the bottom.
Well, then
We can use that paper to display other places
Let's move those over here!
Move all the tourist spots around the world here!
Which attractions should we move first?
Where did Mom go?
It must be the supermarket she usually goes to!
The supermarket is at the corner of the bakery!
No, wait a moment
I remember the bakery and the fish shop were swapped
Where is the fish shop?
I don't know anymore.
Officer!
Excuse me, where is the supermarket?
I'm sorry
I don't even know where the police box is
This won't do
It must be over there!
It must be Gian and Suneo messing with the map again
We need to find Mom quickly now!
Right
Since we're changing it anyway, why not make it an international city?
Okay!
I remember turning left at this laundromat
Huh?
Mr. Yamada's house reconstruction is gorgeous
I remember, after passing through this alley
should be the shopping street
Buongiorno, signora
Buongior...
Signorina, feel free to look and shop
Yes, the weather is great today.
Where is this place?
Even the Statue of Liberty...
At this point, all we can do is go to the sky to find Mom
The mountain behind turned into a pyramid!
Strong and robust, incredibly impressive!
My name is Gian!
With all my heart, I have high tension!
I am a little overlord!
Debut to the whole world!
Gian is here!
Gian and his gang are causing chaos
Mom!
Nobita, Doraemon!
Mom, I miss you so much
This is outrageous!
Restore everything immediately!
- I'm really sorry!
This belongs here, this belongs here
Is the Eiffel Tower in Egypt?
It's in France
I have no idea what to put where
I'm going to school!
Great, I won't be late today
How could this happen? I have no idea
The school building was rebuilt?
It seems we left the school here
I'm so tired
[Advertising with a Mirror]
Mom, can I have an extra 300 yen for allowance?
No, you need to save your money through to the end of the month
Mom, please help me out
There's a manga I really want to buy
- There's a monster!
It's the same monster as before!
What's going on?
I did a little experiment
"Image Projection Mirror"
The image that this mirror reflects
will also be displayed on other mirrors
its projection range can be adjusted at will
from the house to the entire town
Set to automatic mode
It will automatically project when someone looks in the mirror
You really scared me just now!
That's right
I was so scared my heart almost jumped out
So sorry
But what's the use of this gadget of yours?
It's completely useless
At most, it can be used to scare people like just now
Actually, keeping it here is also quite useless
Break it, then
Wait!
That would be a pity
Let's think about it more
Maybe we can think of a good use for it?
What? I don't think it's possible
What use could it possibly have?
I think it should be useful
I still can't think of anything
The latest issue of the "Happy Bug" comic
This month's cover looks like this
That comic I really want to read
I've got it, I've thought of a great use!
It's advertising!
Let's get all the stores's advertisements!
Then we'll broadcast advertisements on all the mirrors in the city!
So that's it!
Nobita, you're so smart!
We can make some money!
Like this
A 15-second ad costs the client 100 yen
There are 60 minutes in an hour
So that means…
Oh dear, it might take a whole hour to calculate how much!
That's 24,000 yen
That much?
If there's that much
The comics I couldn't buy before, I can buy them now!
We can even eat red bean paste buns as much as we want
Alright!
We'll start looking for advertising clients tomorrow!
Okay!
Since we're going to look for advertising clients
We should dress more presentably
- We're leaving!
Hello!
Sorry to bother you!
Advertising?
Yes, as long as you use this image projector
you can project it onto nearby mirrors
and advertise the products you want to promote!
Doraemon
Yes, yes
Look, it's like this
But I don't need it
Nobody actually looks in the mirror all the time
Sir, please don't worry
It's not just mirrors
Glass and shiny floors
Anything reflective can project!
It's here too!
But advertising with mirrors feels unrealistic
Let's just forget it!
Don't say that
There will definitely be many customers
Welcome!
We have customers!
Please go
How could this happen?
Using mirrors for promotion?
With such good business, why promote?
We are already very busy
Using mirrors for promotion?
These kinds of sales tactics...
We are not interested
Our shop doesn't need it
We don't need it
-No thank you, please leave quickly
-No thank you
- We don't need it, please go.
- Hey, get outta here...
It seems finding advertising clients is really hard
Using mirrors to advertise, to attract attention
I think this method is clearly good
Complaining is not the solution
First, we advertise using mirrors
We'll promote it ourselves
That's right
In that case
Let's just advertise for one shop
Is that okay?
As long as it goes smoothly, the other shops
will definitely look for us to use mirror advertising!
That's my Nobita, you're especially sharp today!
Only today? Am I not usually sharp?
I think we should find shops that aren't doing so well
All the shops are doing great business
Let's try looking in the side streets
What about that shop?
Sounds good
It's run-down and deserted
It looks like it could close down at any moment.
It's simply a
perfect shop for advertising and promotion!
Excuse me.
Run-down and could close down at any moment...
Are you the owner of the shop?
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's true
Well, the shop does look run-down on the outside
But it's actually very clean
That's true
It's sparkling
Even the floor is spotless
Come, are you interested in trying some?
Such beautiful wagashi
The colors look very beautiful
Wagashi are not only tasty
They also have beautiful appearances
And a seasonal feel and delicate craftsmanship
Then I'll help myself
Wow, this is delicious!
- Yummy!
That soft and rich sweetness fills my mouth!
Oh, yeah?
In that case, please try the red bean bun too
Red bean bun, I'll help myself!
The bun is very soft, with delicate red bean paste
This is exquisite!
But even if it tastes so good
why aren't customers coming to eat here?
Ever since the big street outside was rebuilt
into a new shopping street
absolutely no customers have been coming to buy stuff.
Originally, I had thought about renovating the shop
But there are simply no customers coming
It's really quite a headache
Please rest easy, leave it to me!
Let's make advertisements for Araware
And turn this place into the bustling
most popular shop!
Impossible
Also, I don't have the money to film commercials
I won't charge any fees
We hope as many people as possible can know that this shop
Has such delicious red bean buns and wagashi!
Could that really work?
Alright
The broadcast range will be set to the entire city
Well, then
The promotion will use these two types of wagashi, right?
Yes
But you don't even have a camera
How can we film the advertisement?
Leave it to us
Doraemon, are you ready?
Ready
Let's start then!
Counting down five seconds
Four, three, two, one
Start!
What do you think of this one?
With a big mirror attached
Araware's wagashi are the triple crown of wagashi!
Red bean buns are on a big sale!
Red bean buns are only 80 yen!
Araware's red bean buns are usually not available for 80 yen!
Hey, what's going on?
In short, it's very delicious, great value, and number one in Japan!
Nobita, you're so mean!
Araware...
- Araware...
Nobita, those two?
Customers should be coming soon
Why isn't anyone coming?
Let me go see what's going on
There are no customers
Here it is!
It's that kid!
Here they come, customers!
Get him!
How could this happen?
Why is everyone so angry?
Nobita, hurry over here!
- Doraemon!
- Don't run...
Strange
Ads like that are a total nuisance!
That scared me
Hurry back
Huh, everyone's angry?
Yes
That's why I didn't really want to advertise in the first place
It's really asking for trouble
- I'm sorry
Now customers will be even less likely to come
What should we do now?
If customers don't come and buy stuff
this shop will close down very soon!
It's our fault!
- I'm sorry...
The one who should be crying is me
Forget it, it doesn't matter
Please don't cry anymore
Actually, this month is when I originally planned
to close the shop
Mr. Araware
If you don't mind
Please eat as much as you want of the pastries in the shop
How can we accept this?
We clearly couldn't help you at all
And you still treat us to a meal?
Even though it was only for a moment, I was very happy
Thank you all very much
And also, the way you ate with such enjoyment
I really want to see it once more
- Yes
Help yourselves
- Bon appetit!
It's so tasty!
So tasty, I can't stop eating!
Another skewer!
No fair, I want one too!
- Yum!
Looks delicious
Over there
This pomelo cake is really tasty!
It’s the one from earlier
Kintsuba is also the best in the world!
- Mom, buy that one for me
- I can't believe how tasty it is
So happy!
That place is... Araware?
I can't take it anymore, I need to go out for a bit.
I'm going too.
Hey, where are you guys going?
I'm so full
I'm already so full
You're full? There's still a lot left.
Excuse me, I'd like to buy kintsuba.
I want red bean buns and kintsuba.
Welcome!
Yes, coming right up!
Why are there suddenly so many people?
It's this!
The image projection mirror has been on the whole time, filming us
Is that so?
Please, everyone, do not push!
- Thank you... Welcome, everyone!
- Here are your red bean buns.
This is too great, Mr. Araware.
Yes, it's all thanks to you two!
Thank you!
Okay, these are yours
Sha la la la la
Accompany me to sing together
Singing loudly
Let's go have fun and step together
Doraemon
Let this moment not get old
Beautiful scenery can be seen