[Ninja Hattori-Kun is Always Right]
Kenichi
Classmate Yumeko
Tomorrow, you all
are you going to play baseball against the ghost team?
That's right
Yes, I will definitely cheer for you all then
You must try your best
I will go to the stadium no matter what, goodbye
Oh no, that's bad
If I play well, of course I welcome them to watch
The problem is that I play so poorly
Okay, let's practice hard.
Oh no, I'm really playing poorly.
Oh dear, that's strange.
-I clearly saw someone just now
-It's Kin Jai
Is that Ninja Hattori?
My baseball skills are about the same as my ninja magic.
Are they really similar?
Alright, I'll be the pitcher now.
Hit the ball for me to see.
Nin... Ninja!
Why is your posture so weird?
I'm going to throw it
Hold it in...
Oh, that's amazing
Okay, now we're going to practice catching. Put on your glove
I don't need to wear a glove
Okay
Look, I'm going to throw it now
Oops, it's the Earth!
Hold it in…
It's a pinball!
Endure...
Wow, you're amazing, Little Sprite
Please, please be my coach, promise me
Here, Master Little Sprite
I'll kneel and beg you at most
Here, please by tomorrow
Make me a baseball player
Huh? You want to become a good player in a day?
Kenji, look at what these are.
Are these red beans?
That's right
-Are you trying to make red bean soup?
-No
I mean when I practice my swordsmanship
You have to concentrate and stare at the red bean
It's very strange
When you stare at the bean for a long time
That bean will naturally get bigger
And then
Whether it's red beans or rice
It can be cut in half immediately.
As big as a baseball.
It should be easy to hit, right?
That makes a lot of sense.
Okay.
Sigh, since it's like that...
I won't sleep tonight no matter what. I have to stare at the red bean all night.
Why doesn't the red bean get bigger no matter how much I stare at it?
It's very simple, because your skills aren't good enough.
Oh no, this is bad...
Oh no, of course I fell asleep last night without realizing it.
The... the red bean, oh no.
- Oh no, it looks really big.
- Then what about this baseball?
It looks quite big.
It looks bigger, which means you...
Oh no, I finally succeeded.
Oh no, this is really too much.
Little clever one, thank you so much.
Today I will definitely... hiss, I can be the star of the show.
Jian Zai, why aren't you up yet at this hour?
Oh dear, it's already 8 o'clock, eh?
Oh dear, why is it such a big red bean?
How did you get it?
Oh, so Mommy can also see it's a big one?
Oh dear, so it's an artificial red bean?
I understand now, you little imp
You want to make me full of confidence, don't you?
Hold on...
Kin Zai!
Oh dear, Mommy, please tell him I have a cold
I can't participate in the competition, oh no.
Everyone, I am truly very sorry.
Endure...
It's Kin Jai.
You have a cold and are still participating in the competition?
Missed three times.
Eight people in a row have already been eliminated by missing.
Oh no, next is Kin Jai.
Kin Jai, you have to keep going!
It's Kin Jai's turn to appear.
He wins less than he loses
His pose is so weird
No wonder Kin Zai knows he can't hit it three times
So he just went wild
Well done, it's a home run
Wow, amazing
Ouch... why... why is it like this?
-Wow, well done!
-Come on Kin Zai, come on!
Endure...
Well done Kin Zai
Oh no, what happened? Oh no...
Eh... aren't these my jerseys?
Who is it, really?
- It's Kin Zai...
Let's put it on first
Kin Zai, where have you been?
It's your turn to play now
We'll definitely win if we just get one more point
Kin Zai, you need to try harder
Oh no, why is it down to the wire
- It's my turn already?
- One, two, three, three, two, one
Kin Jai will definitely make it
Oh no, we've lost all face anyway
Might as well go crazy
Why is Kin Jai playing again?
He's my nemesis today
Oh no, the ball is too fast, I can't hit it
Great shot
Oh no, he totally doesn't take me seriously
How can this be?
Well done
Great! Our team won!
Great! We only won today thanks to you!
Kin Jai, you're really great, Kin Jai
No, I was just...
You don't have to be so humble, you definitely held something back
- You're great
- You're really amazing
A little trick was all it took to get it done
[Transfer student from Kōka]
Classmates
This is our new classmate, Jin Mak-kei, who just transferred to our school
Please give me your guidance.
He looks quite honest.
Hey... do you want to play baseball with us?
Oh, I don't know how to play.
He looks like a woman.
Be careful!
Hey, I'll catch it.
You're so good at catching balls?
It was just luck.
Really?
Yes, Classmate Golden Mak Kai
What? You know how to embroider?
Yes… Yes, Classmate Yau Mei
Wow, that's beautiful
If you like it, I'll give it to you
Really? You're giving it to me?
Thank you
Kin Jai, Golden Mak Kai's handicraft is really good
It's passable, I guess
Oh no, what should I do?
I'm wearing my new shoes today, so I don't want to get them wet.
Look, if you step over my schoolbag, they won't get wet.
Oh dear, this person is not only pretentious
-…but also hypocritical
-You're too kind.
What are you thanking me for?
Thank you so much.
You're really too kind.
You're welcome, it's my duty.
Alright, classmate King Mak-kai, goodbye.
See you tomorrow morning.
Oh no, why are you doing this?
He... he didn't say 'goodbye' to me?
Oh no!
Why did you suddenly change into a different person?
I have a split personality, so it's not strange at all.
Your tone of voice has become fierce.
Come on, give me a massage.
You should be joking.
For no reason, why do you want me to give you a massage?
Fine, you're not giving me a massage.
I will give you a massage
Don't squeeze me
Behave yourself
The teacher is coming
Oh, switch positions
What are you two doing?
Eh... like this
Because Ken's classmate takes good care of me in all aspects
So I'm giving him a massage
Hey, Ken
Why would you want a classmate to act like this?
Teacher, I didn't.
You're not allowed to say that.
Don't you know your responsibility is to
guide the transfer students?
That was really fun just now.
I don't think it was fun at all, I'm leaving.
Hey, wait a moment.
I'll grace your place with a visit.
I'm back.
Son, you're back?
Mom, this is my classmate Kim Mak-kei
Sorry to bother you
I am truly very envious
Kin-zai, you have such a gentle and beautiful sister
Oops, she's not my sister, she's my mommy
Oh really?
Do I really look that young?
Look, this is my room
Oops, what are you doing?
This is my room.
Hey, what are you doing?
You go in first!
Where is it now?
That's right, it's here.
Iga ninja, watch out, come out!
Ow, bear it!
Oh no, don't...
Don't do that.
Watch out!
Kin-zai, what are you guys doing in the room?
Oh no, don't hit anymore
Stop it, Mom is coming!
Look at this move, smoke screen!
Oh no, why is there so much smoke in the room? What are you doing?
- What happened to you, classmate Golden麦基?
- A strange younger brother bullied me
Oh no, is it the little spirit?
Endure...
How can this be?
How can you bully such an honest child?
Oh, Mother, I didn't bully him
As a punishment, you are not allowed to have dim sum
Auntie, please forgive them
Because I am here
They are my first pair of friends
I can't bear to leave them
You are so hypocritical
Back in school
Because I was too honest and too kind
No one wanted to be friends with me
This makes me so lonely
Oh, how pathetic
Jian Zai
I want you to be good friends with classmate Jin Mai Ji
Remember that
Oh, who on earth is that Jin Mai Ji?
He is a ninja from the Kōka school
Our Iga school and Kōka school ninjas
are mortal enemies
No wonder
When they saw you just now,
they were practically blinded by rage.
Hey, I haven't settled the score with you for yesterday yet!
I challenge the Iga ninja from your house to a duel!
Dueling is a barbaric act, why must you do this?
-Why not just be friends?
-Hmph, you scoundrel!
Do you want me to hit you again?
So the Iga ninja was hiding here, was he?
That's right, in order to protect me,
she always accompanies me to school.
This is great, let's duel here
This is a school, how can we duel here?
Take this!
No, don't do this you guys
Stop fighting, hey, stop it
What's all the noise about?
Kin Jai
You called classmate Kam Mak Kai again today
To give you a massage, is that it?
There's no such thing
Student Kam Mak-kei, come here
Oh no, where did it go?
Where did student Kam Mak-kei go?
Hey, Kin-zai
How dare you!
To actually play a trick on the teacher
No, I didn't
It has nothing to do with me at all
In the end, I'll be mad at the teacher again
We'll settle this another day
Little Ling-lung comes to pay respects.
Hey... wait a moment, kid.
Hey, give me the bus fare, the bus fare.
Look.
Oh no!
Hey, wait a minute...
Hey, bus fare, you haven't given me the bus fare yet.
This move is called smoke screen.
Alright, what's going on?
Look up there.
Hey, hey, kid, you're in danger.
Stay right there and don't move.
I'm coming to save you now.
That's all for now.
Hey, no, don't jump!
Oh no, don't jump!
Oh no, it's dangerous.
Oh no, this is really bad.
I have a fear of heights.
Kin Jai and Siu Ling Jing.
Where have they gone now?
They've gone out to play
Oh, no wonder the house is so quiet
Oh dear, I'm so tired, let me sit down first
It's delicious
Hey, Xiao Lu, who are you?
Oh dear, where is it?
Huh? What are you looking for?
Of course it's upstairs
Upstairs?
You don't have it? Oh dear
No, it's not here either
It's not there either, and not here... where did it go?
Where? This is infuriating
Her cries are truly terrifying
She's really giving me a headache
Don't do that, don't cry
Where is it?
Ah, over there
Who on earth is this child?
I think this child must have something special about them
Oh, it's Golden Macaque again?
Little Sprite, I must defeat you today.
Oh no, Golden Macaque, don't fight.
Don't be noisy, Little Sprite.
If you don't want Jian Zai to get hurt,
then hurry up and compete with me.
Who is it? Come out.
Oh no, Little Ling Lung?
Little Ling Lung...
Hey, it's Poodle?
Hey, brother, let me help you
Oh, the little demon's child is here?
That's right, I am the little demon's child
Oh my, is that the little demon's child?
Now let me help my brother
I'm going to take you down
It's just a petty trick
Oh my, it turns out to be a dart made of bamboo?
I'm not a formal ninja
So I can't carry lethal darts
Alright, let me show you the awesome skills of a true ninja.
How are you? Are you okay?
Let me deal with him.
Brother, let me defeat him by myself.
Huh, I didn't expect this kid to be so boastful.
We haven't decided the winner yet.
That's all... hurry up and cry...
What now? Do you know how formidable the Kōka school is now?
Damn it.
Do you know how formidable I am?
Ouch... My head feels like it's about to split open from you shaking it
Ouch, what's wrong?
My weapon is powerful, isn't it? Surrender yet?
I surrender, I surrender
Your secret weapon is really powerful
Compared to my brother's kung fu
It's really a small thing compared to a big one
Jian Zai, let me introduce you
This is my little one, his name is...
Of course, if you cry, you'll faint from crying
Oh, so it’s the little sprite’s kid?
I knew there was a connection a long time ago
Let’s keep him here, okay?
Our family has now become five people
Sigh, this is going to be really lively
Mom, where did you go?
Why did you leave me like this?
Oh no, he’s about to cry out
Don’t let him cry at all
Quickly change the channel
Oh no, I have to change it again
Here it comes
Oh no, Mummy, don't die
Don't leave us behind
Who says I'm stupid?
I say you're stupider than a roasted goose
Are you that clever?
Who's cooler than me?
How are you cooler? Tell me quickly!
I'm the coolest, you're stupid!
You haven't seen it? Awesome!
Are you that capable?
It's going to be troublesome after Xiao Linglong arrives.