[Shishimaru Joins the Fight]
Kenichi, wait for me
Zero again?
You're not loyal enough for a day!
If you were willing to let me peek, this wouldn't happen
How can you cheat?
If you don't want a zero
then study harder!
Ah, you sound just like Mommy
I'm so scared!
Oh, calm down, no need to be scared
This dog is on a leash
Huh, what are you going to do about it?
Oh no, it's not on a leash anymore
Kenichi, you're a big strong man
- What are you afraid of?
- Save me!
Wow, that's amazing
Awesome!
Kenichi, you're acting tough
This puppy...
You are truly amazing!
Ah, what a waste of time
That puppy won't talk to you anyway
Wait a moment!
It's gone?
I don't know where it ran off to
It looks kinda like that
The dog you drew doesn't even look like a dog
Hey, don't criticize me
That's right, I remember it had something on its forehead like a...
A shuriken
Oh, could it be…
But that's impossible
Hattori-kun, so you've seen him?
Oh no, no, I haven't
But I will try my best to help you find him
Uh… excuse me
Seems like Shishimaru has really come
I originally left him back at my village
I really didn't expect him
Yan…
Oh, I don't need to look for Shishimaru.
I just need to use food to lure him in.
Ah, Shishimaru.
Who told you to come here?
So outrageous, go back to the village!
You know, I'm not in Tokyo for fun
I'm here to learn.
Oh? It's a ninja technique, the bone-dissecting, shrinking, escaping net method.
I didn't expect your technique to improve so much.
Excuse me...
But you can't stay here.
You will affect Kenichi's family life.
Well... Okay, I'll let you stay here.
Tomorrow, no matter what, you have to go back to the village, understand?
Oh my, who is it?
Who on earth ate all my rice?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
I cooked a big pot of rice, why is it all gone?
- I don't know.
No need to ask, it must be Shishimaru
Oh no, Shishimaru
Oh, where did the dog come from? Is it from Hattori-kun?
Yes, I'm so sorry
Tomorrow I will definitely send it back to the village
Oh, wait
I recognize this dog, it's my savior!
Please don't make him go
Let's let him stay here
But Shishimaru is greedy and rude
He'll cause you a lot of trouble.
This dog is so clever.
Why don't we keep him? Okay, Mom?
But I'm afraid...
Although he is very greedy, he is really very clever.
Okay, let's keep him.
Tomorrow, we'll build him a doghouse, okay?
Hooray!
They're so nice to you, why don't you thank them?
After a couple compliments he's already beside himself with joy.
He's lovely, my parents have decided to take him in.
Really?
I actually liked him a lot too.
But he's Hattori-kun's friend, don't break them up.
Ah, what's that sound?
That snore is so loud the whole street can hear it.
Hey, Shishimaru, please
Shishimaru, this bed is for me to sleep in.
Having Shishimaru around is really troublesome.
[The Goal is Full Points]
Okay, the test is tomorrow
Oh no, another test
Don't be noisy... hurry up and get in order
You don't need to be nervous
Reviewing homework as usual is enough
Yes!
People who get zero on the exam
answer particularly loudly
Oh no, as long as I work hard, I will definitely pass
As long as I pass, no one will laugh at me, okay!
I'm back!
Yan...
What's wrong with Kenichi today?
He didn't even glance at the afternoon snacks.
How about I take them to him? Here.
Yan...
Hey, Kenichi, open the door!
You're not eating such delicious snacks?
Are you feeling sick?
Is the goal to get full marks? Oh, I understand now.
Your approach is very...
I see you have so much determination
I will help you achieve your wish, don't worry
Hattori-kun, thank you so much
Alright, I must get full marks tomorrow
- Kenichi, come out and play ball
Oh, hold on a moment
Let me help push them away
You should study hard, you can't play now
It's not too late to study after I play
Why are you acting like that?
Just kidding.
Oh, Shishimaru
You don't believe me, do you?
I really can do what I say I can do.
Kenichi knows how to study hard, so exciting!
Of course, I always got zero on tests and people laughed at me.
Alright then, if you get good grades, I'll give you a prize.
Really?
Okay, tonight I'll study all the way until dawn.
- Okay, I'm full.
- I'm full too.
Oh, nice!
- You just promised Mum you'd study.
- Oh, let me see for a moment.
- You can't watch TV, yan...
- It doesn't matter
Oh dear, the show will be over soon.
A real man should be able to do it.
A word once spoken can't be taken back.
Even so
What's the use of cramming at the last minute?
The math is hard.
Hey, don't go!
Kenichi
You must fully commit to study successfully
Ah... Got it...
Maybe I'm too strict
But I'm only doing it for your own good
Ah, I understand
But it shouldn't matter if I sleep a bit
You can't! You should know
you can't get full marks
- You're so embarrassing, hurry up
- Oh, Hattori-kun
I'm so hungry now, please.
Oh right, if you're hungry
you'll have no energy to study.
Okay, I'll get you something to eat.
So annoying!
Yan... Huh?
Fire!
Shishimaru, that's a bit much!
I'm so tired from studying for so long.
- Still not enough
- Yeah... huh?
Oh, now it's a perfect score.
- I just want...
- Kenichi... are you in the bathroom?
Yes...
Ah, fine. Since I can't sleep
I might as well study until dawn.
Watching for cars, okay?
Okay
Yan... Huh? He's dozing off?
Kenichi, Kenichi!
Hey, you can't be snoozing
Seize the moment, wake up quickly!
Oh, this is bad
Finally woke him up
Kenichi's results are really unexpected
Finally success!
Congratulations, Kenichi, you did very well
Kenichi, congratulations
Here, this is your prize
How can I accept such a big prize?
Huh, what are
you saying?
It was hard work to get Kenichi good results
Kenichi, here, this is yours
So small?
Alright, we can eat now.
Ah, Hattori-kun, you got off well
- Such a big prize?
- Kenichi, why don't we trade?
Oh my, you'd really trade with me?
An encyclopedia...
So it's a quartz watch? That's great.
Mom is really smart.
Kenichi fell for it
Yan...
［Yours Truly, Cooking Expert］
Ah, Mommy, just rest a bit.
Today, the two of us will cook for you.
Go rest.
What are you talking about?
Today isn't Mother's Day or Father's Day.
Why are you doing this?
You usually work hard.
Today we want to repay you.
Is it really to repay me?
Okay, Mom, don't say anymore, go...
Why don't you just sit here and rest first?
Fortunately, Mom didn't notice or think much of it.
If we perform well this time,
next month we can ask her
to give us more pocket money.
Yan...
Be careful, cut slowly.
Is this how you cut it?
It won't be ready until morning.
Here, throw it to me then!
What? Throw the ingredients to you?
Come, let me demonstrate!
Ah, I get it now
For Hattori-Kun
- it's a piece of cake. Here it comes!
- Yan!
Amazing!
Wow, amazing!
This move is called "Radish Quick Knife Chop!"
Ah, you're really something
Alright then!
Time to chop vegetables, catch this!
My sword skills are all-powerful.
Chop onions!
Radishes!
Here it comes...
Next off, we're chopping pork
Spam! Oh, there's still... oh my.
Hey, chop this! Here, vermicelli.
The vermicelli is too soft, can't cut it.
Oh no, it's all cut up now.
Why are we cooking so much?
Give me more!
Let me eat more...
Oh, what's going on?
Oh, is Kenichi's family planning a party?
Oh, right, what kind of party is it?
Could it be Kenichi's birthday?
Or is it Hattori-kun's birthday, so...
Oh, I get it.
It must be Shishimaru's welcome party!
Really? Then I'll join too.
- I'm going too!
- I might as well go.
Oh, why cook so many dishes?
Hey, don't ask so many questions.
Hurry up and sit down first.
Oh, what day is it today?
Why make so many dishes?
I heard Kenichi and Hattori-kun worked together to make them.
- Good evening
Who are you guys?
Thank you so much for inviting us to attend
What? You're saying I invited you to a party?
Today, um... isn't it Shishimaru's welcome party?
No
Today is my dad and mom's wedding anniversary
Oh dear, I really forgot
-Today is a big day!
-I completely forgot too!
Shishimaru
It's not a party for you at all
Why are you just making things up?
I'm very sorry.
But it doesn't matter, everyone, please come in and sit down.
Please go in, go ahead.
That's right.
Since we've prepared so much food anyway
Please everyone, come and eat.
- Uncle and Auntie, congratulations!
Thank you so much, thank you all!
Kenichi and Hattori-Kun, it's so rare to see you so enthusiastic.
It's nothing, but I have a small request.
We'd like you to increase our allowance next season.
You two really have a complete plan.
How could we possibly refuse?
That's right, let's agree to it.
- Our strategy is a success! Time to eat!
- We won!
- Let's eat!
Hey, hurry up and eat.
- Wow, if he eats that fast, he'll finish it all!
- He ate it all!
Wow, he'll finish it all so easily.
So fast?
Shishimaru, how can you be so lazy after eating?
Hurry up and help with the chores.
Don't be a gluttonous lazybones!
Hey, Mommy,
hurry up and rest.
Let us finish the leftovers, you go to bed.
Okay, thanks for your help.
Yan...
So many dishes to wash, how long will it take?
Don't worry, we had to do the cooking.
So Shishimaru is responsible for washing the dishes.
What? W... what?
Woah, that's right, Shishimaru didn't do anything at all
You ate so much, it's only fair you wash the dishes
Yan...
Ah, Shishimaru is actually quite good at washing dishes
Actually, when Shishimaru does work, he's really very capable
Oh no, this is bad, how did this happen?
Your help celebrating my wedding anniversary made me very happy
But... this is really too disappointing
Kenichi, you must compensate all the smashed dishes
Next month, I'll deduct it from your allowance
That's only fair
- Hurry up and clean up!
- Oh no, this is miserable!
Shishimaru, you're the one who got us into this
It's all your fault
I'm sorry
We were supposed to have more pocket money
But it backfired